all-athletics.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy policy | All-Athletics.com

All-Athletics.com considers very important the distribution of the information of public interest and at the same time the protection of the personal data and its confidential treatment. The personal and public data are treated by All-Athletics.com according to the Hungarian Law, ( Avtv.1992./LXIII) and the relevant declarations of the Data Protection Commisar of the Parliament.

You do not have to provide any personal data to reach the free contents of the website. The restricted contents are available only for the subscribers. During the first section of the subscribing process the subscriber registers himself/herself and it is neccessary to provide some personal data. The payment procedure is technically completed on the website of the K&H Bank, thus the subscribers’ credit card information is not reachable for All-Athletics.com.

Any personal data recieved by All-Athletics.com will be treated confidentially and will not be disclosed to any third party whatsoever, except for the cases defined by the Law. The personal information received by All-Athletics.com will be used only for the purpose which you have asked us to use them for, and will not be disclosed for any other purpose.

All-Athletics.com will hold all personal data securely and will protect it by any legal way.

All-Athletics.com receives the following automaticaly generated information about the user of the website: interprotocoll address of the user (IP address), the date and time of the visit, the browser program used by the visitor. All-Athletics.com will use them only for analyzis relating to the website, following the trends and statistical information.

This site may contain external links that will provide you with information or bring you to the web page of a third party. All-Athletics.com has no control over the information that you may receive through such links and their operation policy, and does not endorse your use of such third party web pages and the information provided thereby. All-Athletics.com is not responsible for the accuracy, completeness, timeliness, reliability, content or availability of any information received by you as a result of your use of the site; loss or damage to your records or data; or your use of, or results achieved from any information received by you as a result of your use of the site.
